# **Adam Hyde**

Contact
<a href="mailto:adamjameshyde88@hotmail.com">adamjameshyde88@hotmail.com</a>
0416 042 794

Doolandella, 4077

Brisbane City



# **ABOUT ME**

My name is Adam, I was born on the 10th of July 1988 (currently 31) and am looking forward to starting a fresh new role. I have always been neat, tidy and well mannered. I strive to excel in all tasks of my work to the best of my ability.

I work well in a team as well as unsupervised. I have several years Team Leading experience and I have no problems working under pressure or to strict time frames. I am available to work 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.

# **OBJECTIVES**

To gain a full time position that will enable me to commence a long term rewarding career and make a positive contribution to the company I am working for.

#### **CREDENTIALS**

**Major Training Group - 2019** 

Certificate 1 in Construction (CPC10111)

Included Units (CPCCWHS1001, CPCCOHS2001A, CPCCCM1012A, CPCCCM1014A, CPCCCM1013A, CPCCCM1015A, CPCCCM2001A, CPCCM2006B, CPCCM2004A, CPCCM2005B, CPCCVE1011A)

**Express Online Training - 2019** 

White Card

Get Skilled Australia - 2019

Forklift Licence

**Aspley State High School - 2003** 

**Year 10 Certificate** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Team Leader/Customer Service | Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre (AEG Ogden) November 2008 - January 2019

My previous position at the Convention Centre has helped me to develop and mature in the workplace. Although primarily situated in one home department I took advantage of multi hire opportunities to learn more skills and gain more hours of employment. I was Team Leading for my home department Front of House and have experience working within Building Services, Floor Coordinators as well as Security. I am also proud to say that I was given the opportunity to work hands on with a mega scale and significant event for Brisbane - the G20 World Leaders Summit.

# Some duties of employment included -

- Allocation of resources and responsibilities amongst staff during event setup often with tight turnarounds
- Liaising with clientele and venue staff to ensure smooth event progress as Floor Coordinator
- Setup and dismantling of event furniture (tables, chairs, concert stage, dance floor and other various theming)
- Cross checking of the provided event floor plans and staff rostering to ensure sufficient resources
- Team Leading which included training other staff members and helping colleagues to set higher standards of work

Customer Service | Factory Takeaway Geebung April 2007 - August 2008

Customer Service Assistant, Cook and Kitchen Hand

**Customer Service** | Brisbane Airport (Spotless) June 2004 - February 2007 While employed by Spotless I worked in several of their specialty outlets in the Virgin Blue Terminal, Brisbane Domestic Airport.

#### Zaps

Food Preparation, Kiosk Cleanliness

#### **Espresso Plus**

Cafe Assistant and Barista Operator

# Eat 'n' Runway

Client Service

#### **Red Rooster**

Customer Service Assistant, Cook and Kitchen Hand

# TRANSFERABLE SKILLS I CAN BRING TO YOUR COMPANY

- Computer Literate
- Customer Service
- Cash handling and eftpos operation
- Food preparation
- Stock management
- Storeman duties
- Espresso machine operation
- Workplace health and safety
- Workplace hygiene
- Spotter for heavy machinery
- Portering (freight logistics)
- Ability to safely use an electric or manual pallet jack
- Forklift Licence
- Sico stage assembly
- Shell Scheme booth and wall building/dismantling
- Room and event setup
- Previous Team Leading skills
  - Delegation of tasks
  - Time management
  - o Effective leadership
  - Motivation of staff
  - Ability to adapt under pressure
  - Make independent decisions
  - Eye for detail
  - Reading and interpretation of Floor Plans
- Driver's Licence
  - o with my own reliable vehicle

# PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

- Professional and mature attitude
- Can work well independently and as part of a team
- Flexible
- Ability to multitask
- Self motivated
- Committed
- Reliable
- Willing to learn
- Honest
- Budget conscious

# **REFERENCES**

Robert Gravolin | Sets Manager - Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre Mobile - 0402 684 522

Mark Griffin | Sets Team Leader - Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre Mobile - 0405 454 299

Ryan Cheal | Sets Team Leader - Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre Mobile - 0458 469 458

Sam Houston | Driver - Country Club Hotel Dalby Mobile - 0438 726 040

# **IN SUMMARY**

I am looking for an employer who will help me develop my skills in a friendly and positive working environment. Ultimately I would hope career advancement is available as I am looking for long term rewarding and career developing employment.

I ask that you consider me for an interview so that I can show you in person the type of dedicated and friendly employee I would be. I am sure that given the opportunity that I would exceed your expectations and represent your business in a positive and professional manner.